http://www.constructionbook.com/privacy-policy

ASE – Automotive Service Excellence
ASHRAE – American Society of Heating, Refrigerating, & Air-Conditioning Engineers
PHCC – Plumbing - Heating - Cooling Contractors Association
SMACNA – Sheet Metal & Air Conditioning Contractors' National Association
ASE – Automotive Service Excellence
ASHRAE – American Society of Heating, Refrigerating, & Air-Conditioning Engineers
PHCC – Plumbing - Heating - Cooling Contractors Association
SMACNA – Sheet Metal & Air Conditioning Contractors' National Association
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.constructionbook.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.
We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-800-253-0541 or via email at customersupport@constructionbook.com
You can order from constructionbook.com with confidence because all purchases are 100% guaranteed! If you are not completely satisfied with your order, simply return the product to us within 30 days for a full refund of the purchase price.
